(Just For Love)
（只为爱）
(Episode 6)
（第6集）
Eat it. I want to go back.
吃了它。我想回去。
Do you want to go home and wait for Miss Zheng?
你要回家 等郑小姐吗？
Did I say something wrong?
我说错什么了吗？
Didn't you say…
你不是说……
you don't want to talk about personal things at work?
你不想 在工作中谈论私人事情吗？
Would it be too sudden if I went looking for him?
我去找他会不会太突然了？
He will get angry and trouble me more later?
以后他会生气，更加麻烦我吗？
The situation has become like this.
情况就变成这样了。
Zheng Shu Yi, you cannot lose.
Zheng Shu Yi, you cannot lose.
Who cares whether he will be angry or not?
谁在乎 他会不会生气呢？
I must get a specific response today.
我今天必须得到 具体答复。
Miss Zheng, why did you come to see me at this time?
郑小姐，你怎么 这个时候来找我啊？
My draft is already like this.
我的草稿已经是这样了。
You don't know what this is about?
你不知道这是关于什么的吗？
I just feel that...
我只是觉得...
you might want to see me, so I came looking for you.
你可能想见我， 所以我来找你。
Try to tell me.
尝试告诉我。
Why do you think I want to see you?
你认为我为什么 想见你？
If not, why did you reject my draft three times ?
如果不是的话，你为什么三次拒绝我的草稿？
Oh, I see?
我懂了？
You can stand it, you are confident and firm.
你能承受，你有信心，你坚定。
Your logic flows smoothly.
你的逻辑很流畅。
I almost thought so too.
我也差点这么想了。
My draft,
我的草稿，
even my author and editor-in-chief…
甚至我的作者和主编……
the most critical in the financial journalism industry…
财经新闻行业最关键的……
can't even find any mistakes.
甚至找不到 任何错误。
But you turned him down three times...
但你却拒绝了他三次...
without giving any specific feedback.
没有给出任何 具体反馈。
Is there any reason other than to see me?
除了来看我还有什么理由吗？
My reason is…
我的理由是……
I'm not satisfied.
我不满意。
Not satisfied?
不满意？
What are you not satisfied with?
你还有什么不满意的？
Show me any issues, and I'll check them until you're satisfied.
有任何问题请告诉我，我会 检查直到您满意为止。
If you can't say what you are not satisfied with,
如果不满意的话不能说出来
that proves that you want to meet me.
这证明你 想见我。
You deliberately used this way to get my attention,
你故意用这样的方式 来引起我的注意，
so that I can come to see you.
这样我就可以来看 你了。
In the first draft, there were many words that were too complimentary.
在初稿中，有很多 过于恭维的话。
I believe an excellent personal interview …
我相信这是一次出色的个人采访……
should be different from normal corporate PR material.
应与 正常的企业公关材料不同。
Writing should be more rational and objective.
写作应该 更加理性、客观。
Journalists can have their choice,
记者可以有自己的选择，
but that should not affect the reader's reading and thinking.
但这不应该影响 读者的阅读和思考。
You should be aware of this problem.
你应该 意识到这个问题。
So, in the second draft, you change it to an objective article.
所以，在二稿的时候，你 把它改成一篇客观的文章。
You don't miss any content.
您不会错过 任何内容。
However, because you care too much…
然而，因为 你太在意了……
about its perfection and objectivity,
关于其完美性 和客观性，
the draft lacks emphasis.
该草案缺乏重点。
The focus of this interview should be Yunchuang's future,
这次采访的重点应该 是云创的未来，
not the Mingyu Group, and certainly not my personal development.
不是明宇集团，更 不是我个人的发展。
So, what about the latest draft? What is the problem?
那么，最新的草案呢？问题是什么？
You put a lot of effort into that draft,
你为这份草案付出了很多努力，
and many issues have been fixed.
并且许多问题已得到解决。
But I think there should be room for discussion.
但我认为应该有 讨论的空间。
I still remember saying this in the car that day.
我还记得 那天在车上说过这句话。
I believe in the company's technical ability and innovation…
我相信 公司的技术能力和创新能力……
to some extent determine its competitiveness and core development.
一定程度上决定了 其竞争力和核心发展。
I express this view to facilitate discussion,
我表达这个观点 是为了方便讨论，
not to draw conclusions.
不得出结论。
Therefore, I think when you produce an official article,
所以我觉得当你 写一篇官方文章的时候，
should more faithfully represent my true expression and attitude.
应该更忠实地代表 我的真实表达和态度。
I humbly accept your opinion.
我虚心 接受你的意见。
This fact is not clear enough as I wrote,
正如我所写，这个事实还不够清楚，
but everyone has a different interpretation.
但每个人都有 不同的解释。
You can't ask me to rewrite it…
你不能 要求我重写它......
whole article just because of one issue.
整篇文章 只是因为一个问题。
The draft has been delayed for a long time.
该草案已被推迟很长时间。
If I don't hand it over quickly,
如果我不快点交出来
our magazine has no cover story this time.
我们的杂志这次没有封面故事。
I really want to write this article well.
我真的很想 好好写这篇文章。
Please help me.
请帮我。
Yunchuang is a very reputable company…
云创是一家 非常有信誉的公司……
and always pursue thoroughness.
并始终追求彻底。
Due to different interpretations,
由于解读不同，
you have written my words in a more absolute way,
你把我的话写得 更绝对了
represent my personal views and judgments.
代表我个人的观点和判断。
But what I want to explore more is the potential of this industry.
但我更想探索的 是这个行业的潜力。
It means completely different,
意思完全不一样，
and the generated impact will certainly be much different.
所产生的影响 肯定会大不相同。
I understand what you mean now.
我现在明白你的意思了。
If so, I'll fix it now.
如果是这样，我 现在就修复它。
Come here.
过来。
Don't you want to redo the draft?
你不想 重做草稿吗？
Fix it inside.
把它修在里面。
Isn't it difficult to fix the draft at home at this time?
这个时候在家修稿子不是很难吗？
What if I run into his nephew again?
万一再碰到他侄子怎么办？
Mr. Shi, is it okay for me to go to your house at this time?
石先生，我这个时候去你家可以吗？
You have come to my house.
你来 我家了。
Now you're starting to worry if this bothers me?
现在你开始担心 这是否会困扰我？
I'm just excited to revise the draft.
我很高兴 能够修改草案。
Don't worry, no one can bother you.
别担心，没有人 可以打扰你。
You can definitely fix it to my satisfaction.
你绝对可以修到 令我满意的程度。
He actually came here to re-correct the draft.
他来这里其实是 为了重新修改草稿的。
Yue, are you sure this will work?
悦，你确定这行得通吗？
Why not?
为什么不？
This gift is amazing even for my uncle and aunt.
即使对于我的叔叔和阿姨来说，这份礼物也很棒 。
This wine is really good.
这酒确实不错。
But I advise you not to have high hopes.
但我劝你 不要抱太大希望。
If he knows you gave him this wine so he won't make you work,
如果他知道你给他 这酒是为了不让你工作
I don't know how he will react.
我不知道 他会作何反应。
Why don't you give me this wine?
你为什么不给 我这酒？
Do not waste.
不要浪费。
Don't be shy.
别害羞。
I hope this will save me from this desperate situation.
我希望这能让 我摆脱这种绝望的境地。
You don't want to help me,
你不想帮我，
even my grandfather doesn't want to help me.
连我爷爷都不愿意帮我。
This bottle of wine is my only savior.
这瓶酒是 我唯一的救星。
what do you want to drink
你想喝什么
Lemon juice, thank you.
柠檬汁，谢谢。
Thank you, Mr. Shi.
谢谢施先生。
He has a good memory.
他记忆力很好。
Why?
为什么？
Are you having any problems?
您有什么问题吗？
So.
所以。
So, what's the problem?
所以有什么问题？
I want…
我想…
drink the drink you're holding.
喝掉你手里拿着的饮料。
Thank You.
谢谢。
He immediately didn't look at me.
他立即没有看我。
It seems that this lipstick color is not effective.
看来这个口红颜色 效果并不好。
Helo?
你好？
I'm very busy. That's inconvenient.
我很忙。那很不方便。
Don't, sir!
别这样，先生！
Mistress?
情妇？
Why?
为什么？
Does anyone want to come?
有人想来吗？
So.
所以。
Does your niece want to go back?
你侄女想回去吗？
You seem very interested in my niece.
你看起来 对我侄女很感兴趣。
No, why?
没有为什么？
I don't know him.
我不认识他。
He said he was very busy and troublesome.
他说他很忙 ，也很麻烦。
He said the same thing when I called him that day.
那天我给他打电话时他也说了同样的话。
What trouble is there for a man?
男人有什么烦恼呢？
But he's with a woman.
但他和一个女人在一起了。
I think your uncle must be hiding the girl in his house.
我想你叔叔一定 把那个女孩藏在他家里了。
Hide girls in his house?
把女孩藏在他家里？
It's been three years.
已经三年了。
Finally, my uncle fell in love with someone.
终于，叔叔 爱上了一个人。
Have you ever met that girl?
你见过那个女孩吗？
Shi Yan didn't let me see him. Where can I find him?
施言不让我见他。 我在哪里可以找到他？
Did you ever see him bring his girlfriend back?
你见过他 带女朋友回来吗？
It's ready. Look at it.
准备好了。看它。
What kind of?
什么样的？
Too long.
太长。
Okay.
好的。
I can't believe I can't fix it again.
我不敢相信我 无法再次修复它。
I have summarized.
我已经总结了。
Mr. Shi, please check if there is any problem.
石先生，请检查一下 是否有问题。
That's not what I mean when I say this.
当我这么说时，我的意思不是这个 。
If so, what do you mean?
如果是这样， 你是什么意思？
Think for yourself.
为你自己想想。
Why don't I write to you straight away?
我为什么不 立即写信给你呢？
Okey.
好的。
Really?
真的吗？
Really nothing to fix again?
真的没有什么可以 修复的吗？
Approximately.
大约。
If you are satisfied,
如果您满意的话，
does that mean we can go further?
这是否意味着我们 可以走得更远？
Go further?
更进一步？
Go further…
更进一步……
to explore the possibility of a special coverage.
探索 特别报道的可能性。
Since you are satisfied with my draft,
既然你 对我的草稿感到满意，
surely you will be satisfied with…
一定会让您满意的……
my proofreading service too.
我的校对服务 也是如此。
So, can you consider the special coverage I mentioned earlier?
那么，您能考虑一下 我之前提到的特别报道吗？
If I go further with you,
如果我能 和你一起走得更远
what benefits are offered?
提供什么好处？
If you accept my proposal,
如果你接受我的建议
I will definitely prepare the articles for this series well.
我一定会好好准备 这个系列的文章。
I guarantee you will be satisfied.
我保证你会满意的。
But…
但…
I have a small request.
我有一个小小的请求。
I hope these articles can be published…
我希望这些文章 能够发表……
in the Financial Introduction digital magazine.
在 《金融简介》数字杂志中。
Is this how journalists in Financial Introduction do business?
这就是 《财经导论》记者的工作方式吗？
I have not agreed to your interview for special coverage,
我还没有同意接受 你的特别报道采访，
and you have made additional demands.
并且您 提出了额外的要求。
Sorry for not thinking.
抱歉没有思考。
I should have taken it step by step…
我应该一步一步来的……
and discuss this after completing this interview.
并 在完成这次采访后讨论这个问题。
Did I say something that offended him?
我是否说了一些 冒犯他的话？
Mr. Shi said…
石先生说……
he doesn't like to discuss personal matters during work hours…
他不喜欢在工作时间讨论私人问题……
and at work.
在工作中。
That's right.
这是正确的。
He doesn't like to discuss personal matters…
他不喜欢 讨论私人问题……
during working hours and at work.
在工作时间 和工作中。
He may not like to discuss work matters…
他可能不喜欢 讨论工作问题……
during private time and in private space as well.
在私人时间和 私人空间也是如此。
Mr. Shi, please consider my suggestion.
石先生，请 考虑一下我的建议。
Also, can you send me an email confirming the draft now?
另外，你现在可以给我发一封电子邮件 确认草稿吗？
Follow the procedure,
遵循程序，
this should be confirmed by our company's PR Department.
这应该得到 我们公司公关部门的确认。
I will check it again tomorrow.
我明天再检查一下。
All right, Mr. Shi.
好的，石先生。
If you have any problems tomorrow, just let me know.
如果 明天你有任何问题，请告诉我。
I have no problem. I can cooperate and fix it again.
我没有问题。我可以 配合并再次修复。
Are you sure there is no problem?
你确定没有问题吗？
I'm sure there is no problem.
我确信没有问题。
You sit so long…
你坐那么久……
at the house of a man I don't know very well late at night.
深夜在一个我不太熟悉的男人家里。
Your boyfriend has no problem with it?
你男朋友 没问题吧？
I don't have a boyfriend.
我没有男朋友。
That's right.
这是正确的。
The first day I met you,
遇见你的第一天 ，
I broke up with him after I came back.
回来后我就和他分手了。
On the day of the Guan Capital ceremony, outside the Warner Property.
冠都典礼当天， 华纳地产外。
You still remember, don't you?
你还记得，不是吗？
So?
所以？
So…
所以…
can i chase you
我可以追你吗
If I say no,
如果我说不，
will you stop
你会停下来吗
So.
所以。
So why are you asking me?
那你为什么问我？
I just followed the procedure…
我只是按照程序进行...
to show you respect.
以表达 对您的尊重。
Thank you for respecting me.
谢谢你对 我的尊重。
The draft is finished. You can go now.
草案已完成。 你现在可以离开了。
Mr. Shi, good night.
石先生，晚安。
I will add you on WeChat when I get back.
回来后我加你微信。
I can chat with you when you are bored.
你无聊的时候我可以陪你聊天。
I am very good at chatting. I have a lot of emoji stickers.
我很擅长聊天。 我有很多表情符号贴纸。
Let me remind you one last time.
让我 最后提醒你一次。
Your uncle will not be happy if you show up at this time.
你这个时候出现你叔叔会不高兴的。
I do not care.
我不在乎。
I want to see who that girl is.
我想看看那个女孩是谁。
My uncle never brought his girlfriend back before.
我叔叔 以前从来没有带过他的女朋友回来。
I want to see who that extraordinary woman is.
我倒要看看， 那个非凡的女人是谁。
How do you know my uncle's mood is good because he's in love,
你怎么知道舅舅心情 好是因为恋爱了，
he won't tell me to go to work.
他不会叫我去上班。
It's strange.
真奇怪。
Shouldn't he be busy re-correcting the draft?
他不是应该 忙着重新修改草稿吗？
What is he doing here?
他在这里做什么？
Who's that?
那是谁？
Why?
为什么？
My uncle did not allow me to reveal my identity.
我叔叔不允许 我透露我的身份。
Everyone knows that you are the young master of the Guan family.
大家都知道，你 是关家的少爷。
I don't want to be involved with you.
我不想和你扯上关系。
Who's that?
那是谁？
He is the senior I told you about.
他就是我跟你说的那位前辈 。
He criticizes me a lot.
他批评我很多。
The value for journalists is so high now?
现在记者的身价 这么高了？
I advise you not to have any ill will towards him.
我劝你不要 对他有任何恶意。
My uncle doesn't like him.
我叔叔不喜欢他。
He rejected the draft several times.
他多次拒绝了该草案。
Of course, especially because you love me so much.
当然，尤其是因为 你如此爱我。
where is he
他在哪里
Where is that girl?
那个女孩在哪里？
Lipstick?
口红？
There is indeed a woman.
确实有一个女人。
Why did you come here?
你为什么来这里？
Didn't I tell you to go back to your grandfather's house?
我不是叫你 回你爷爷家去吗？
I came to deliver this wine to aunt.
我是来 给阿姨送这酒的。
Good things should be sent to uncle as soon as possible.
好东西要 尽快送给叔叔。
What if you are too busy and don't have time to...
如果你太忙 没有时间怎么办？
eat at grandpa's house?
去爷爷家吃饭吗？
Just park here and come back early to rest,
就停在这里然后 早点回来休息吧
don't get up to work tomorrow.
明天别起床 去上班。
You better have self-awareness to be an employee now.
作为一名员工，你现在最好有自我意识。
Uncle, why don't you ask the girl to stay the night?
叔叔，要不请 姑娘留下来过夜吧？
What girl?
什么女孩？
The woman that uncle and aunt just drank with.
刚才和叔叔婶婶一起喝酒的那个女人。
It's very late, why didn't you tell him to stay the night?
这么晚了， 你怎么不叫他留下来过夜呢？
Is it because she's not pretty enough?
是因为她不够漂亮吗？
Or did he reject you?
还是他拒绝了你？
Or maybe…
或者可能…
It's been a long time since you've been in love until you're scared now?
已经很久没有谈恋爱了， 现在才开始害怕？
What's wrong with Shi Yan?
施言怎么了？
Right, right?
是的是的？
This is the first time I express my feelings to someone in my life.
这是我一生中第一次向某人表达自己的感受。
and he kicked me out after hearing that.
他 听后把我赶了出去。
Is this reasonable?
这合理吗？
Is Shi Yan a man?
施言是男的吗？
Now I'm sure he's a man,
现在我确信 他是个男人
he's just a childish man.
他只是一个 孩子气的人。
- Shi Yan childish? - Yes.
- Shi Yan childish? - Yes.
Have you ever heard of "men are forever young"?
你听说过 “男人永远年轻”吗？
When they are not honest with themselves,
当他们对自己不诚实时，
women will have no chance.
女性将没有机会。
Have you never read a novel about an arrogant CEO?
你没读过一本 关于傲慢总裁的小说吗？
The more the man likes you, the more he doesn't want to admit it.
男人越喜欢你， 他就越不愿意承认。
The more he likes you, the more he wants to bully you.
他越喜欢你， 就越想欺负你。
Shi Yan is that kind of man.
石岩就是这样的人。
Qin Shi Yue.
Qin Shi Yue.
What nonsense is playing in your mind?
你脑子里在胡思乱想什么？
Uncle invited him to drink at home this late at night.
这么晚了，叔叔请他到家里喝酒。
After drinking, uncle told him to leave,
喝完酒后，叔叔 叫他走，
without spending some time together.
没有花 一些时间在一起。
Oh God.
天啊。
Is this man itchy?
这个男人痒吗？
You're talking about itchy guys.
你说的是那些发痒的家伙。
That's about it.
就是这样。
Try to understand it.
尝试去理解它。
If not, why will he keep rejecting your draft?
如果不是的话， 他为什么会一直拒绝你的选秀呢？
Because…
因为…
there is an issue with my draft.
我的草稿有问题。
Of course, that's part of the reason.
当然，这也是部分 原因。
But the most important thing is that he wants to attract your attention.
但最重要的是 他想引起你的注意。
He must be interested in you.
他一定对你感兴趣。
I really admire your inexplicable confidence.
我真的很佩服 你莫名的自信。
This is a conclusion I have come to through many practical experiences.
这是我通过多次实践经验得出的结论 。
As the saying goes, experience is the best teacher.
俗话说， 经验是最好的老师。
Although the trick is a bit old, but effective.
虽然这个招数 有点老了，但是很有效。
But why do you…
但你为什么……
suddenly expressed feelings to him today?
今天突然 向他表达了感情？
Maybe you have fallen in love with him.
也许你已经 爱上他了。
How could it be?
怎么会这样？
I did that for my article.
我为我的文章这样做了。
You didn't tell me to…
你没有告诉我要...
So why do I feel like something is wrong?
那么为什么我感觉 有些不对劲呢？
The two of you are alone and the atmosphere feels attractive.
两人独处 ，气氛让人觉得很有吸引力。
And you suddenly expressed your feelings to him.
而你突然 向他表达了你的感受。
Could it be that you have been attracted to him for a long time without realizing it?
难道你已经被他吸引很久了而不自知吗？
Think carefully about what I'm saying.
仔细想想我说的话。
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
我不想 再和你说话了。
I want to go back. I have to work tomorrow.
我想回去。 我明天还得上班。
To be honest, I think he's interested in you too.
说实话，我觉得他 也对你感兴趣。
If you are both interested, what are you waiting for?
如果你们都感兴趣， 还等什么？
Grab this opportunity before you miss it.
抓住这个机会，以免错过。
- Goodbye.
- 再见。
Use up food, don't waste it.
把食物用完，不要浪费。
When it comes to love, you need to learn from Guan Ji.
说到爱情， 你需要向管吉学习。
Don't be insensitive.
不要麻木不仁。
If you really like it, you need to take the initiative.
如果你真的喜欢它， 你就需要采取主动。
If you invite him to come,
如果你邀请他来，
You should take this opportunity before you miss it.
你应该抓住 这个机会，以免错过。
You still have time to fool around here.
你还有时间 在这里胡闹。
It seems that working at the magazine company is really easy.
看来在 杂志公司工作真的很轻松。
This is how.
就是这样。
Come and continue working in Yunchuang.
来云创继续工作吧。
Stop being lazy.
别再偷懒了。
That's okay, thank you.
没关系，谢谢。
Uncle, rest early.
叔叔早点休息吧
Working at a magazine company is not easy at all.
在杂志公司工作 一点也不轻松。
I didn't finish work until after eight o'clock today.
今天我直到八点多才完成工作。
I'm busy all day.
我一整天都很忙。
I work hard and take it very seriously.
我努力工作并且 非常认真地对待它。
I need to go back and rest.
我需要回去休息。
Don't make a sad face in front of me.
别 在我面前露出悲伤的表情。
Not effective.
没有效果。
Also…
还…
Save your money for this wine.
省点钱买这款酒吧。
(Thinking calmly)
（冷静地思考）
Shi Yan didn't say I can't chase him,
施言没说 我不能追他，
so he agreed without saying a word.
于是他二话不说就答应了。
What am I waiting for?
我还在等什么？
(Searching. The user does not exist.)
（正在搜索。 该用户不存在。）
Mr. Shi, how afraid are you that others will find your WeChat account?
石先生，你有多害怕别人 找到你的微信账号？
I have reached home.
我已经到家了。
Mr. Shi, are you asleep?
石先生，你睡了吗？
I think you must be very busy.
我想你一定很忙。
You only need to read the first three sentences of the previous message.
您只需阅读 上一条消息的前三句即可。
I saw this online.
我在网上看到这个。
It can express my feelings without being too ridiculous.
既能表达 我的感受，又不会太可笑。
Just perfect.
刚刚好。
Today will be cloudy with light rain tonight,
今天多云，今晚有小雨，
with temperatures ranging from 5 to 12°C.
温度范围为 5 至 12°C。
Tomorrow will be cloudy changing to partly cloudy,
明天多云转晴 间多云，
with a temperature between 3 and 10°C.
温度在 3 至 10°C 之间。
There will be continuous rain in the coming days,
未来几天将持续阴雨天气，
coincides with the work week.
与工作周重合。
Don't forget to plan your trip accordingly.
不要忘记 相应地计划您的旅行。
Make sure to stay warm.
确保保持温暖。
Mr. and Mrs.
先生和夫人。
When it comes to love, you need to learn from Guan Ji.
说到爱情， 你需要向管吉学习。
Don't be insensitive.
不要麻木不仁。
If you really like it, you need to take the initiative.
如果你真的喜欢它， 你就需要采取主动。
If you invite him to come,
如果你邀请他来，
You should take this opportunity before you miss it.
你应该抓住 这个机会，以免错过。
(Actress)
（演员）
Nyahlanggan?
尼亚朗甘？
Shi Yan, what about you?
石岩，你呢？
Mr. Shi, I just got a call from Le'an Technology.
石先生，我刚刚接到 乐安科技的电话。
They said they have reviewed our financing group plan.
他们说他们已经审查了 我们的融资集团计划。
Mr. Chen said…
陈先生说……
while the funding pool provides some reassurance…
虽然资金池 提供了一些保证……
for their future research and development,
为了他们未来的研究和发展，
there is still quite a big gap…
差距还是蛮大的……
compared to Lieying's acquisition price at the current level.
与目前猎鹰收购价格相比。
So, they are very concerned about the solution…
所以，他们非常 关心解决方案……
to the technical issue you mentioned during the day.
关于你白天提到的技术问题。
Mr. Shi, our final offer is the highest price…
史先生， 我们的最终报价是最高价……
that we can give.
我们可以给予。
Even if there is an increase, it cannot match the acquisition price.
即使有增长，也无法 匹配收购价格。
If we continue to be stranded here,
如果我们继续被困在这里
will that lead to change?
这会带来 改变吗？
I understand. Go to work first.
我明白。先去上班吧。
do you have time Let's meet and talk.
你有时间吗 我们见面谈谈吧。
Shu Yi, good morning.
Shu Yi, good morning.
Good morning, Shi Yue.
Good morning, Shi Yue.
Why?
为什么？
Nothing.
没有什么。
Your lipstick looks beautiful.
你的口红看起来很漂亮。
Take it.
拿去。
I…
我…
Not that.
不是那个。
He usually never used colors like that.
他通常从不 使用这样的颜色。
It seems that Zheng Shu Yi's draft was rejected several times by Yunchuang.
看来郑书仪的稿子 被云创拒绝了好几次。
He had never been in a situation like this before.
他以前从未遇到过 这样的情况。
How do you know he didn't offend anyone?
你怎么知道他没有 得罪任何人？
Encountering a client who rejects a draft without giving feedback…
遇到一个客户拒绝草稿 而不提供反馈......
very difficult.
非常困难。
So, uncle is indeed my biological uncle.
所以，叔叔确实是 我的亲叔叔。
But Zheng Shu Yi might not be that woman.
但郑淑仪 或许不是那个女人。
Who deliberately makes their loved ones suffer?
是谁故意让 自己的亲人受苦呢？
Is that humane?
这有人性吗？
But…
但…
My aunt may like this.
我阿姨可能会喜欢这个。
I think he can do that.
我认为他可以 做到这一点。
Zheng Shu Yi.
Zheng Shu Yi.
Can you stop being so diligent?
你能别 这么勤奋吗？
At least give us a break.
至少 让我们休息一下。
Guaranteeing Guan's Capital was an important step for Mingyu Yunchuang.
保住关氏京城，是 明宇云创迈出的重要一步。
Capital Guan invited Yu You back here at this time.
关都 此时将余幽请回了这里。
And Shi Yan went to his welcome party.
而施言也去参加了 他的欢迎会。
You have chosen the next topic.
您已选择下一个主题。
You didn't give us a chance.
你没有给我们机会。
Why? Have you taken care of Shi Yan?
为什么？你照顾好施言了吗？
Approximately.
大约。
Yu You's opinion should be important for the decision of Guan Capital.
于友的意见对于冠资本的决定应该很重要。
Talking to him will surely give many clues.
和他交谈肯定会 得到很多线索。
Actually, it's not hard to guess what Shi Yan wants to do.
其实，不难猜测 施言想要做什么。
But the key is how he will continue each step.
但关键是 他将如何继续每一步。
Readers must be very interested in this.
读者一定 对此非常感兴趣。
Good. All 10 loops.
好的。全部 10 个循环。
Rock climbing day duration. This time, shoot.
攀岩一天的持续时间。 这一次，射击。
You really don't look like a college professor.
你看起来根本不像 大学教授。
You also don't look like a rich second generation.
你看起来也不像 富二代。
Actually, Bruce is also quite different.
事实上，布鲁斯也很不同。
What kind of difference?
有什么样的区别？
The domestic market is vast,
国内市场广阔，
and the terms you offered Bruce were very attractive.
你给布鲁斯提供的条件 非常有吸引力。
Many people would consider this a good choice.
很多人会认为 这是一个不错的选择。
But Bruce is just like me.
但布鲁斯就像我一样。
He loves excitement, adventure, and challenge.
他喜欢刺激、 冒险和挑战。
So, pay and conditions are not…
所以，工资和条件不......
the main factors to consider.
主要 考虑因素。
So, don't try to predict or judge him with fixed thoughts.
所以，不要试图 用固定的想法来预测或判断他。
He will come next week.
他下周会来。
Have you thought of a way to convince him?
你有没有想过如何 说服他？
Do you have any suggestions?
你有什么建议吗？
We both like to do interesting and challenging things.
我们都喜欢做 有趣且有挑战性的事情。
Actually, so did Bruce.
事实上，布鲁斯也是如此。
Exciting and challenging, both are indispensable.
刺激和挑战， 两者缺一不可。
So, why are you willing to go back to China?
那么， 你为什么愿意回中国呢？
Actually, the academic environment is getting better here.
事实上， 这里的学术环境越来越好。
And I also get to know friends like you and Guan Ji.
我也认识了 像你和管吉这样的朋友。
Speaking of which, you are very attractive.
说起来， 你很有魅力。
What you do is also very challenging.
你所做的事情 也非常具有挑战性。
You can accept Mingyu Group's offer and make everyone happy,
你能接受 明宇集团的报价，让大家都高兴，
but you chose to start your own business…
但你选择了 自己创业……
and established Yunchuang.
并成立云创。
Isn't it fun working with you?
和你一起工作不是很有趣吗？
Apparently I'm so annoying, huh?
看来我真的很 烦人啊？
But I believe if I can pull you back to China,
但我相信如果我 能把你拉回中国
I can definitely pull Bruce too.
我也绝对能拉布鲁斯。
And I'm sure Bruce will be amazed by Chen Kang's enthusiasm.
我相信布鲁斯会对 陈康的热情感到惊讶。
Sorry, I have to answer this call.
抱歉，我必须接这个电话。
Helo.
你好。
Professor Yu, saya Zheng Shu Yi.
Professor Yu, saya Zheng Shu Yi.
I wonder if you still remember me.
我不知道 你是否还记得我。
Miss Zheng, of course I remember you.
郑小姐， 我当然记得你。
Here, the duration of the day is too hasty,
这里，一天的时间 过得太匆忙，
and I didn't have time to talk to you.
我没有时间和 你说话。
I want to schedule time with you next week…
我想 和你安排下周的时间…
to ask you some questions about the industry.
向您询问 一些有关该行业的问题。
Okay, okay.
好吧好吧。
Let me check my schedule and get back to you later.
让我检查一下我的日程安排， 稍后再回复您。
OK, thank you very much.
好的，非常感谢。
Good.
好的。
can i chase you
我可以追你吗
Come on, one more round.
来吧，再来一轮。
Ms. Yi, I have reviewed my interview article with Guan Ji.
易女士，我已经审阅了 我对管吉的采访文章。
Ready for layout and printing.
准备好 布局和打印。
Cik Yi?
Cik Yi?
Ms. Yi, Mr. Shi has already confirmed verbally.
易女士，石先生已经 口头确认了。
Yunchuang will respond officially soon.
云创将于近期正式回应。
This version of the article should be okay.
这个版本的文章应该没问题。
Shu Yi, we understand that you have worked hard this time,
舒怡，我们明白你 这次辛苦了，
but we need to take into account the overall situation.
但我们需要 顾全大局。
Can we rely on verbal confirmation?
我们可以依靠 口头确认吗？
Front page content is not child's play.
首页内容 不是儿戏。
If mistakes happen, the responsibility will be great.
如果发生错误， 责任就很大。
I am confident in my article.
我对我的文章很有信心。
And Mr. Shi also promised…
而石先生也答应了……
will email me confirmation today.
今天会 向我发送电子邮件确认。
What good is your faith now?
现在你的信仰有什么好处呢？
If there is a problem, how will you be responsible?
如果出了问题， 你如何负责？
Are you going to resign?
你要辞职吗？
Since he agreed to reply by today,
既然他同意 在今天之前回复，
let's wait until midnight.
让我们等到 午夜吧。
If there is no answer or not approved by Yunchuang,
如果没有答复或 未经云创认可，
so we will use Yu Ling's article as the front cover.
所以我们就用余凌的文章 作为封面。
I have no problem with that.
对于那件事我没有任何疑问。
How about you?
你呢？
I have no problem either.
我也没有问题。
You looked less focused earlier.
早些时候你看起来不太专注。
Not like your usual standard.
不像你平常的标准。
Mr. Shi, this is important.
石先生，这很重要。
You confirmed my draft yesterday.
你 昨天确认了我的草稿。
Please send me a confirmation as soon as possible.
请 尽快给我发送确认信息。
Really? Let's do another round.
真的吗？让我们再进行一轮。
Ms. Zheng, Mr. Shi is not with me today.
郑女士，石先生 今天不在。
He might be busy. I can't even contact him.
他可能很忙。 我什至联系不上他。
I can't help you.
我帮不了你。
(Storage room)
（储存室）
It's too late now.
现在已经太晚了。
So why not approved?
那么为什么不被批准呢？
What are we waiting for here?
我们还在这里等什么？
What can we do?
我们可以做什么？
We work in the news industry. We have to be careful.
我们从事 新闻行业。我们必须小心。
We agreed to wait until 12 midnight, so just wait,
我们约定等到 午夜12点，所以就等吧，
not even a minute less.
一分钟也不少。